看我又在邮箱里发现了什么
Look what someone left in our mailbox -- again.
等等 这是第五朵了吧
Wait, that's like our fifth one, isn't it?
越来越恐怖了
It's getting kind of creepy.
放松啦 可能是维克托放的
Oh, relax -- it's probably just from Victor,
就是以前跟我约会的送花小哥
that flower-delivery guy I dated.
谁是维克托 我们从没听过他
Who's Victor? We never heard about him.
因为我知道你们不会
Oh, because I knew
让我跟一个有前科的家伙出去的
you'd never let me go out with an ex-con.
也许是迪兰想赢回你的心所以送来的
Hey, maybe it's Dylan trying to win you back.
那么维克托 彻底不可能了吗
So, Victor -- it's a closed door?
可能并不是喜欢海莉的人
Maybe it's not a guy who's in love with Haley.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
可能是某个迷恋海莉的家伙
Maybe it's a guy who's obsessed with Haley
于是打算做整形手术 变成她的样子
and is getting plastic surgery to look like her
这样就可以取代她 过她的生活
so he can replace her and live her life.
卢克
Luke.
就只能是给海莉的吗
So they can only be for Haley?
当然不是
Of course not.
这里又不是只有海莉一个尤物
Haley isn't the only hottie living here.
我前几天穿着我的运动短裤洗车
I washed the car in my cheer shorts the other day.
明显感觉到有人在看我
I definitely felt eyes on me.
你们就没想过那些花可能是给我的吗
Has it ever occurred to you that those flowers could be for me?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是 也许是我男朋友送的
I mean, like, from my boyfriend.
什么
What?
你有男朋友了
You have a boyfriend?
你们居然还觉得我的想法不可思议
And you thought my thing was crazy.
艾丽克斯 你有男朋友了
Alex, you have a boyfriend?
你别就这么撂下一句话就走了啊
You can't just drop that and ave.
亲爱的 太惊喜了
Honey, it is so exciting.
你为什么没告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us?
因为我知道你们会觉得很诡异
Because I knew you'd get all weird
然后问一堆蠢问题
and ask a million stupid questions.
他长什么样 你怎么认识他的
What does he look like? How did you meet him?
我给你们看照片
Okay, I'll show you a photo.
我是想给你们看 但我手机坏了
Well, I would, but now my phone's not working.
对了 这里有他
Oh, here he is.
超市宣传单上嘛
In the supermarket flyer?
就是提着猪排的那个人吗
That's him pondering the pork chops?
有什么好考虑的
What's to ponder?
一磅4.59美元[ponder也有考虑之意]
They're $4.59 a pound.
我不明白 他怎么在这里头
I don't understand. Why is he in this?
他是模特 老妈
He's a model, mom.
等等 你男友是模特
Oh, wait, wait. Your boyfriend's a model?
你怎么认识他的
Well, how did you meet him?
全国优秀学生
There's not much crossover
跟猪排模特能有多少交集啊
for a national honor society student and a pork model.
实际上 说来话长 我
Well, actually, it's a really long story. I...
是他的电话
Oh, well -- it's him.
等等
Hey, hold on.
真是太好了
This is terrific news.
不敢相信她居然没跟我们说男朋友的事
I can't believe she didn't tell us about him.
你不敢相信的就是这个吗
Oh, that's what you can't believe?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
菲尔 真有点怪怪的
Phil, it is a little weird.
突然之间 她就有了个男朋友
I mean, suddenly she has this boyfriend.
她想给我们看手机里的照片
She wants to show us a picture on her phone,
但是又没办法
but she can't,
然后他又神奇般地出现在了今天的报纸里
and magically he's in today's paper?
我都不想说了 海莉
I don't even want to say it. Haley.
她肯定是编的
She's making it up.
她为什么这么做
Why would she do that?
可能我们都不相信
Maybe she's upset
那些玫瑰是给她的 让她很伤心
that none of us thought those roses could be for her.
还记得她有一次
Oh, and remember
找不到舞伴参加返校节吗
when she couldn't get a date for homecoming?
她说她不在乎
She said she didn't care,
但我撞见她在她屋里哭来着
but I caught her crying in her room.
亲爱的 你怎么劝的她
Oh, honey, what did you say to her?
那天我要迟到了 我也就没...
Oh, I-I was super late, so I didn't really...
太可悲了
This is sad.
艾丽克斯有了天大的喜事
Alex has great news
但她的母亲和姐姐居然不相信她
and her own mother and sister don't believe her?
我也想信她
I want to.
我真的相信她
Well, I do believe her.
我要让她请她男朋友到家里吃晚饭
I'm gonna tell her to invite this boyfriend over for dinner,
我会给你们做一道
and I'll be serving a big,
名叫"早就告诉过你了"的大菜
old platter of "I told you so."
太好了
Oh, great.
你还可以做独角兽汉堡和魔法豆子
Maybe you could also serve unicorn burgers and magic beans,
我也要请我男朋友来 野人大脚
and I'll invite my boyfriend, Bigfoot!
还是比迪兰好
Still better than Dylan.
来 我给你准备了个惊喜
Okay. I got a surprise for you.
别是又领了个宝宝吧
It better not be another baby.
沙发后面有什么好玩的吗
Is there something fun behind the couch?
埃德加·范德考夫牌的手工特白沙发
An Edgar Vanderkoff hand-crafted blanc de blanc sofa.
是我们给自己的结婚礼物
It was a wedding gift to ourselves.
我们也是在告诉莉莉
Plus, we're showing lily
我们相信她不会破坏这么美的东西
that we trust her enough to let us have one nice thing.
你这么想的话
When you think about it like that,
那真是给莉莉送了份大礼
it's really a gift for Lily. Yeah.
好吧
Okay, whoa.
只有确定自己是干净的才能坐这沙发
We only get on this couch when we know we're not dirty.
所以我们才给她买这个沙发
That's why we got her the couch.
教她懂得尊重
To teach her about respect.
双腿再分开点
Legs a little wider please.
你的后兜里是一块饼干吗
Is that a cookie in your back pocket?
-是的 -好吧
- Yep. - Okay.
拿出来 慢点
Bup-up-up! Hey, nice and slow.
我正看着呢
Watching that.
既然你在这里 你觉得怎么样
But now that I got you here, what do you think?
之前你穿着大口袋短裤
That you wore cargo shorts
参加我初中毕业仪式
to my middle-school graduation,
去参加狗狗的生日派对
but you're putting on a bow tie
反而戴领结了
for some dog's birthday party.
这是为了好玩啊
It's all good fun.
比恩鲍姆夫妇没法生孩子
The Birnbaums can't have kids.
他们想为伯斯特举办一场盛大派对
They like to do it up big for Buster.
我的五岁生日是在一家炸小牛排店的
I had my fifth birthday in a break room
休息室里度过的 但是伯斯特真幸运
of a Der Wienerschnitzel, but good for buster.
你怎么这么暴躁
Why are you so cranky?
学校里有个孩子搞金字塔骗局
This kid at school ripped me off for 40 bucks
骗了我40块
in a pyramid scheme.
那跟你梳妆台上的
Did this have something to do
破碎的塑料金字塔有关系吗
with that broken plastic pyramid on your dresser?
照片里看起来像是大理石的
It looked like marble in the picture.
天啊
Oh, man.
我长大时你在哪里啊
Where were you when I was growing up?
你到年级教室之前
I'd have had your dice and cigarettes
我就能骗到你的骰子和香烟
before you got to homeroom.
你去哪里上学的 《红男绿女》吗
Where'd you go to school -- "Guys and Dolls"?
虽然你很聪明 但你得更机灵点
Bright as you are, you got to smarten up.
你应该更加怀疑别人
You got to be more suspicious of people.
不要这么容易受骗了
Stop being such a patsy.
我这身打扮参加派对怎么样
How is this for the party?
这是我第一次跟你公园遛狗的朋友们见面
It's my first time meeting your dog-park friends.
很棒 但是小心点
Fantastic, but be careful --
这圈子里有人还是单身呢
Some of these guys are single in the group.
毫不意外
What a surprise.
曼尼 我们不能迟到
Manny, we won't be late.
我给你和乔准备了晚餐
I left dinner for you and Joe,
但是不要吃冰箱里的魔鬼蛋
but don't eat the deviled eggs that are in the refrigerator
因为那是明天野餐吃的
because they're for tomorrow's picnic.
什么野餐 庆祝某人的猫上大学了吗
What picnic -- somebody's cat going to college?
不是 歌洛莉亚的一些朋友拿到了绿卡
No, some of Gloria's friends are getting their green cards.
他们其实人很好
It's actually a nice group.
是啊 他们是认真工作的正派人
Yes, they're very decent, hardworking people.
杰在米拉贝拉的假婚礼上遇见了他们
Jay met them at Mirabelle's fake wedding.
《祖宝》
Zooboo!
不 今天你已经看了六次《祖宝》
No, you've already watched "Zooboo" six times today.
我们要在大屏幕上
We're gonna watch a classic movie
看一部经典电影
right here on the big screen.
你最好让他看他的节目
You better let him watch his show.
不然他会炸毛的
If not, he's gonna freak out.
昨天我关了电视
Yesterday I turned it off,
他咬穿了一颗台球
and he bit through one of the pool balls.
米奇尔
Hey, Mitchell.
你好啊
Hi, uh, um...
布...伦达
B...renda.
你还以为我不记得了 对吧
Yes, you thought I wasn't gonna remember, didn't you?
上班第一周感觉怎么样
So, how's your first week been?
我要离婚了
I'm getting a divorce.
天啊
Oh. God.
是我问的 所以...
Um...well, I did ask, so...
我不想一个人待着 懂吗
It's really hard to be alone, you know?
懂
Yeah.
你知道还有谁也加班吗 史黛丝
Hey, you know who else who stays late is, um, Stacey.
-14个月了 -天啊
- 14 months. - Oh, gosh.
有时候早点抽身也挺好的
Well, sometimes it's good to get in and out fast, though, huh?
我们14个月没做爱了
We haven't had sex in 14 months.
我们结婚20年了
We were married 20 years.
这个数字不错
Well, that's a nice, round number.
是的
Yeah.
我的不宁腿综合症 这是离开的原因吗
My restless leg syndrome, like that's a reason to leave?
你知道 大家都有...
Well, you know, everybody has --
他有好多恶习和无理要求
Especially after all his habits and requests!
我比刘易斯和克拉克远征时
God! I've done more paddling
"划船"划得都多
than Lewis and Clark!
史黛丝 你在吗
Hey, Stace, you out there?
她走了 人们会离开
Oh, she's gone. People leave.
如果我可以做点什么
Well, you know, i-if there's anything
来帮助你
that I can do to help you --
我能和你待在一起吗
Could I stay with you?
什么
What's that?
拉里可以坐在沙发上 而我不行吗
So, Larry's allowed to sit on the couch and I'm not?
拉里是白色的[白人]
Well, Larry is white.
是你们选择的我
Hey, you chose me.
我不是那个意思
Oh, uh, that's not what I meant.
-喂 -好啊 小卡
- Hello? - Hey, Cam.
你记得
So, listen, you remember
我的新同事布伦达对吧
my -- my new friend at work Brenda, right?
谁
Who?
是啊 那个美女
That's right -- the pretty one.
她和她丈夫在闹矛盾
Uh, so, she and her husband are -- are going through some problems at home,
她想知道
and she was wondering
是否可以暂住在我们家
if she might be able to stay at our house.
天哪 当然可以了
Oh, my gosh. Yes, of course.
对了 该死
Oh, shoot and darn it!
我就记得好像有什么事的
I thought we had something.
米奇尔 我知道你在干什么
Mitchell, I know what you're doing.
没办法改期了 对吧
Ahh, there's no way we can reschedule, huh?
战胜你的本能
Fight your instincts.
这是你表现同情心的机会
This is a chance for you to show some real compassion.
-我要吃左洛复[抗抑郁药] -好 好
- I need a zoloft. - Okay. Okay.
你说的我都同意
Well, I agree with all that,
不过 我已经很客气了
but I -- I am being nice!
好吗 我跟她说话
Okay? I -- I-I-I talked to her.
我还问她 有什么我能帮忙的地方
I-I asked her if there was anything I could do to help.
可是 我不是认真的
But I -- I didn't mean it.
谁也不可能是认真的
Nobody ever means it.
米奇尔 你希望自己在这方面有长进的
Mitchell, you want this growth in your life.
所以你才会问她 你只是害怕而已
That's why you asked her. You're just scared.
不 不是 那完全就是个虚伪的提议
No, no, it was a completely hollow offer and --
是的 没错
Yeah, that -- that's right.
好的 乔治和温蒂·哈洛请我们
Okay, George and Wendy Hollow offer
晚上七点半吃晚餐 好的 再见
dinner at 7:30. Okay, bye-bye.
你需要做这件好事 而我也需要它
You need this, and I need something nice
作为可以写在圣诞卡片上的素材
to write about you in our Christmas Letter.
我也爱你 再见
I love you, too. Goodbye.
坏消息 是吗
So...bad news, huh?
是啊 如果你介意吃家常菜的话
Well, only if you hate home cooking.
-你是最好的 -那就
- You're the best! - So --
你好像吃进去一点我的左洛复了
I think you got some of my zoloft.
没关系 我用得上
That's okay. I could use it.
狗狗的成年礼 这概念太好了
Bark Mitzvah -- what a concept.
贝狗饼夹熏鱼 狗胸饼
Beagles and lox, dog briskets.
负责这些文字游戏的人真是太赞了
Whoever's in charge of the wordplay, bravo.
这是给狗吃的还是给人吃的
Is this for dogs or for people?
希望是给人吃的 我都吃了四块了
I hope it's for people. I've had four of them.
-你觉得有意思吗 -是的
- Are you having fun? - Ay, yes.
今天前 我还从没见过肉汁喷泉
Before today, I had never seen a gravy fountain.
小软糖 快看 斯黛拉来了
Oh, Gumdrop, look! Stella's here!
大家快来 我们照张合影
Everybody, let's get a picture.
还有狗仔队呢 太棒了
Pupparazzi! How great is that?
大家靠近一点
Everybody squeeze in.
小心她的包囊 她会咬你的
Be careful of her cysts. She'll nip you.
好的
O-okay.
好的 再来一张 小涂鸦刚才眨眼了
Okay, one more. Doodles blinked.
这次靠得再近一些
Now, really get tight this time.
不 不 不
No! No, no, no!
-够了 够了 -歌洛莉亚 歌洛莉亚
- Enough. Enough. - Oh, Gloria -- Gloria.
歌洛莉亚 亲爱的
Gloria, honey, I -- listen.
我知道你不喜欢狗
I-I know you're not a dog person.
不是 跟狗在一起没问题
No, I'm okay with the dogs.
我只是不喜欢爱狗的那些人
I'm just not a dog-person person.
你说这个派对是正常的
You said that this party was going to be normal.
只是图个乐子
It's just fun.
这有个为狗准备的自助餐和酒吧
There's a buffet and an open bar for dogs.
我表亲在救生艇上结的婚
My cousin got married on a raft.
我很努力地融入了 杰
I tried to play along, Jay,
但这也太疯狂了
but -- but this is crazy.
我必须要回家了
I have to go home.
歌洛莉亚 你认为用疯狂这个词
Gloria, now, do you think it's fair
来形容这里公平吗
to use the word "Crazy" about a --
我们回家见 歌洛莉亚
I-I'll see you at home, Gloria.
非常感谢你们
Oh, thank you so much, you guys.
天哪 我寻找真命天子的时候
God, where were you when I was
你们在哪呢
looking for the perfect man?
可能在密苏里
Well, probably in Missouri
一家叫堪萨斯城肉棒的酒吧
at a bar called Kansas City Meats
-做着同样的事吧 -太幽默了
- doing the same thing. - Funny!
-看你笑得 -怎么了
- Look at that smile. - What?
这就是表达善意的感觉
That's what being nice feels like.
-我很喜欢 -我为你骄傲
- I like it. - I'm proud of you.
我只是让一个不怎么认识的人
Well, I'm just letting a person
住在我的家里
I barely know sleep in my home.
我不知道是否可以称得上是英雄 可是
I don't know if I'd use the word "Hero," But...
英雄
"Hero"?
别说了 我都不好意思了
Stop it. You're embarrassing me.
天哪
Oh, god.
你们养猫了吗
Hey, you guys have a cat?
我给你加点酒吧
Um, how about I freshen up that wine, huh?
不用 我很好 好吧
Oh, no. I am good. Okay, um...
事实上 小卡 我们
In fact, Cam, what are --
我们在客厅里待着干什么呢
what are we doing in the living room, here?
你知道吗
You know?
是啊 知道吗
Yeah, oh, you know what?
我们还没带布伦达参观我们的车库呢
We haven't even given Brenda a tour of our ga-- uh, garage.
我们的车库
Our -- our gage.
不去了 我不喜欢车库
Oh, no. I don't like garages.
道格把他心爱的帆船就放在车库里
That's where Doug kept his precious sailboat.
不许在船上吃东西
No eating on the boat.
不许在船上喝酒
No drinking on the boat.
就因为有一次我在船上把酒撒了
All because the one time I went on the boat, I spilled.
-知道吗 船上就是这样 -老天
- Well, guess what. Boats go like this. - Oh, geez.
你知道吗 我当时...
You know?! And I'm like...
谁会爱惜一样东西多过爱惜一个人
Who -- who loves a thing more than a person?
禽兽
A monster.
我们带你看我们的小棚子了吗
Have we shown you our shed?
我们有个小棚子
There's a shed.
他跟我结婚的时候就知道我是什么样的
He knew what he was getting into when he married me.
我有点悲剧
I'm a little messy.
没想到吧 道格
Well, guess what, Doug!
生活本来就是个杯具
Life's a little messy.
我鼻水流个不停 耳朵也会渗出液体
Okay, my sinuses leak, my -- my ears run,
我的汗腺还过度发达
and I have hyperactive sweat glands, but...
我确实需要再来一杯
You know what? I do need a refill.
我一点也不吃惊 她失了不少水
Well, I'm not surprised. She's losing a lot of fluids.
就像道格就在这里一样
It's as if Doug was over here.
我知道 我看到了
I know. I saw that.
艾丽克
Alec!
他的二货爸爸被调去非洲
His dumb dad got transferred to dumb Africa
给一些二货孩子看病
to operate on some dumb babies.
去给他们治心脏就要伤我的心吗
So fixing their hearts is worth breaking mine?
还是挺值得的
It's kind of worth it.
他每天可以做六台手术
He can do like six operations a day.
是 我理解 不好意思我冲你发火了
Yeah. I-I-I understand. I'm sorry I'm lashing out.
我只是太喜欢你了
I-I just really like you.
我还喜欢你
I still like you.
你这么说我感觉更糟
You're making this worse.
再见 艾丽克
Bye, Alec.
再见 艾丽克斯
Bye, Alex.
我就知道你不最后亲我一下是不会走的
I knew you couldn't leave without one last kiss!
我们可以解决这个问题
We can work this out!
我 我会后悔的 对吧
I'm -- I'm -- I'm gonna regret that, aren't I?
我只是想让你帮我丢一下这个
Uh, I was hoping you could throw this away for me.
好 当然
Yeah. Sure.
亲爱的 我们聊了一下
So, honey, we've been talking,
都想见见你男朋友
and we want to meet your boyfriend.
你们刚错过了
You just missed him.
他来了吗
He was here?
他刚走 这是他的杯子
He just left. This is his cup.
瞧瞧这个
Oh, look at that.
这看着像"艾丽克斯"
Oh, it looks like "Alex."
他名叫艾丽克 那个"C"被抹花了
His name is Alec. The "C" Just got smudged.
亲 他叫艾丽克
Honey, his name is Alec.
但那个"C"被抹花了
But the "C" Got smudged.
对了 你怎么不给他发个短信
Yeah, um, well, why don't you just text him
邀请他来吃晚饭
and then invite him back for dinner?
不行 他跟我分手了
I can't. He broke up with me.
不是吧
Oh, no.
他要搬去非洲
He's moving to Africa.
因为非洲的超市需要模特
Because they need grocery models in Africa.
亲爱的 我很遗憾
Honey, I'm so sorry.
他们分手了
They broke up.
我想他
I miss him.
别担心
Oh, don't worry.
很快他就像从没出现过一样了
Soon it will be like he never existed.
好了
Okay.
我的天啊 曼尼 乔怎么了
Ay dios mío, Manny, what's going on with Joe?
他就是个瘾君子
He's a drug addict.
看了两个小时的白痴剧《祖宝》以后
After two hours of mind-liquefying "Zooboo,"
我只是放了一部老电影 他就暴走了
I briefly put on a classic movie, and he freaked out.
要是他走得再稳一点
If he could walk better,
我肯定要推荐个戒毒项目给他
I'd seriously suggest a 12-step program.
不要 乔 不看《祖宝》了
Ay, no, Joe. No more "Zooboo."
谢谢
Thank you.
不要 把大电视关掉
Ay, no. Turn the big TV off.
他看到电视开着就会要看他想看的节目
If he sees it on, he's going to want to watch his show.
你怎么回来了
Why are you home?
伯斯特的派对是个给狗办的犹太成人礼
Buster's party was a bark mitzvah.
我搞不懂杰怎么会带我去那里
I don't know why Jay would take me to this place.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许狗狗派对什么的
Maybe this dog stuff is his way
只是他想找点跟你的共同兴趣
of trying to find a common interest with you.
这不容易
It's hard.
你不喜欢高尔夫或威士忌
You don't like golf or scotch
或者艾森豪威尔的纪录片
or Eisenhower documentaries.
没错 我不喜欢艾克
It's true. I don't like Ike.
可是这个派对上的人
But the people in this party,
他们对狗简直痴迷
they are so obsessed with dogs.
连酒杯都是马桶形状的
Even the punch bowl was in the shape of a toilet.
杰又不是
Well, it's not like Jay
不会为了你做自己不愿做的事
doesn't get out of his comfort zone for you.
他明天要去你的绿卡野餐
He's going to your green-card picnic tomorrow.
你说得对
You're right.
他还给所有人买了带星星的墨西哥宽边帽
He even bought star-spangled sombreros for everybody.
他弄错国家了
It's the wrong country.
他从来不听我说话 不过他很贴心
He never listens, but -- but he's sweet.
你知道吗
You know what?
我该回那个派对去
I should go back to that party.
你们想来吗
You guys want to come?
倒也无妨
Might as well.
我记得伯斯特的割礼上果酱挺好吃的
They had a pretty good spread at Buster's bris.
好了 我们把这个女人弄到床上去
Okay, let's get this woman into bed
明天一早 用最快的速度让她离开
and, in the morning, out of the house as fast as we can.
说实话 我不知道直男是怎么做到的
Honestly, I don't know how straight guys do it.
大概没有这么多手势吧
Probably without those hand gestures.
洗得好吗
So, nice bath?
太舒服了 我准备好上床睡觉了
the best. I'm so ready for bed.
哦对了 我留了个环在里面
Okay. Ooh, by the way, I left a ring in there.
没事 我们明早漂白一下就好了
Oh, well, we'll get at it with some bleach in the morning.
不 不是 是我的婚戒
No, no, no, my wedding ring.
我只是不想再戴着它了
I just don't feel like wearing it anymore.
和讨厌的回忆说再见
Oh, well, goodbye, bad memories,
迎接我们的客用沙发 云端
hello to our guest couch, the Cloud.
真是个小云端
That's a small cloud.
你知道吗 它舒服极了
Oh, you know what? It's deceptively comfy.
我经常在那上面睡觉
I sleep on it all the time.
-是啊 如果我没抢赢他 -真的吗
- Yeah, if I don't beat him to it first. - Really?
好吧 就这样
Oh, okay. All right.
你躺下了
So, there you are.
-好了 -好了 是的
- Okay. - Okay, yeah.
我不...我很确定这不行啊
I'm not -- I'm pretty sure this isn't gonna work.
不 这没事的 没事的
No, no, this will be fine. This will be fine.
我总是这样做的 没什么大不了
This is what I always do. It's not a big deal.
给你布置得舒服一点
Just make this up nice for you.
这样就好了
There we go. Okay.
明早见
See you in the morning.
可是我的 我的头
Yeah, but my -- my head's --
看我们都在想什么呢
Oh. What we were thinking?
来吧 这样就好了
Here. Come on. There it is right there.
-睡吧 晚安 -晚安
- There you go. Okay. Night-night. - Night-night.
两位
Hey, guys.
我有个主意
Here's an idea.
我睡到你们客厅的那个沙发上怎么样
What if I just slept on your couch in the living room?
我在发抖
I'm shaking.
怎么了 问题解决了
Why? Problem solved.
不是 她的呼噜声让整个房子都在抖
No, she's making the whole house shake.
你们回来了 出什么事了
Hey, guys. You're back? What's going on?
对不起 我爱你 而你喜欢这狗派对
I'm sorry. I love you, and you love dog parties.
这就意味着我也喜欢狗派对
So that means that I love dog parties.
你不再认为这很疯狂了吗
You don't think it's crazy anymore?
我没那么说
I didn't say that.
不过曼尼说得对
But Manny's right.
我们应该多参与一下对方的社交活动
We should get more involved in each other's activities.
这是你的主意吗
So, this was your idea?
这应该是健康婚姻生活的基础
Well, it's sort of the foundation of any healthy marriage,
不过是我提出来的
but I did bring it up.
这太棒了
This is great!
来吧 给我搭把手
Well, come on. Give me a hand.
我们给你和你妈妈弄个冰淇淋骨头尝尝
We'll grab you and your mom an ice-cream bone.
我真的没做什么 我只是
I didn't do much. I just --
毁了我的计划 仅此而已
Ruined my plan, that's all.
我希望她离开的
I wanted her to leave!
什么
What?
她本应该怒气冲冲离开这里
She was supposed to storm out of here.
然后 等我回家就可以说
And after, I go home and say,
"也许我们应该分头做事"
"Maybe we should do some things separately."
这样我明天就有借口
I was gonna use her bailing out of this
推掉那个愚蠢的野餐了
as a chip to get out of that stupid picnic tomorrow.
可是现在我没有借口了
But now I've got no chip.
下次你计划想逃避什么的时候
Hey, how about next time you devise a plan
能不能给我点暗示
to avoid expressing a feeling, clue me in.
我不能给你暗示 你脑子太不好使了
You can't be clued in. You're a patsy.
刚才不是说要弄冰淇淋骨头吗
There was talk of an ice-cream bone?
那是我编的 动动脑子好不好
I made that up, too. Use your head!
亲爱的 你一个人吗
Hey, honey, you alone?
你在这里看到别人了吗
Do you see anyone else in here?
你呢
Do you?
宝贝 你爸爸和我觉得该跟你道歉
Sweetheart, your father and I think we owe you an apology.
为了什么
For what?
今早 我们都没想到
Well, this morning when we didn't think
玫瑰花可能是送给你的
the rose could be for you,
看起来有点伤你的心了
it seemed like maybe it hurt your feelings.
我想是有一点
I guess. A little.
我很抱歉让你难受了
I am so sorry to make you feel bad.
你拥有追求者
And it is completely believable
是完全有可能的
that you would have an admirer.
好吧
Okay.
我们担心的是
What we're worried about
我们营造出来的这种氛围
is that we have created an environment
让你觉得有必要...
in which you feel it's necessary to...
-修... -虚...
- embelli-- - fanta--
-夸... -天哪
- exagger-- - Oh, my god.
你们认为艾丽克是我虚构出来的吗
You guys don't think Alec is real?
宝贝 我还记得在高中的时候
Sweetheart, I remember the pressure there was
所承受的那些压力
to fit in in high school.
我也是 不管你是
So do I. And whether you try to fit in
编造说你跟小熊打过架
by saying you fought a baby bear
还是虚构一个男朋友
or by making up a boyfriend...
你们俩真不可理喻
You guys are so unbelievable.
你们真的觉得我悲催到
You really think I'm that pathetic
要编造个幻想男友出来吗
that I'd have to create some imaginary boyfriend?
你知道什么不是幻想出来的吗
You know what's not imaginary?
你的情感
Your feelings.
别 别碰我
Okay, don't! Don't!
告诉你们吧 我刚在Facebook上
F.Y.I., I changed my Facebook
把情感状况改成单身
status to "single"
才改了一个小时 你们猜怎么着
about an hour ago, and guess what.
已经有人约我了
I already have a date.
你们不信我 是不是
You don't believe me, do you?
亲爱的 半分钟内你已经交了两个男友
Sweetheart, you've had two boyfriends in 30 seconds.
几乎破了海莉的纪录
That practically Haley's record.
他是真实存在的 他叫泰迪
Well, he's real. His name is Teddy.
他叫泰迪[熊]吗
His name is...Teddy?
是啊
Yeah.
泰迪·凯斯[钥匙]
Teddy Keyes.
这个年轻人是怎么样一个人
And what do we know about this young man?
他是新转来我们学校的
He's new to our school.
在一个叫"床垫大王"的店打工[马丁·路德·金]
He works at some mattress store -- Mattress King.
还有就是他有些坏男生气质
And he's a bit of a bad boy.
他过去在商店里偷过东西
He had a little problem with shoplifting.
在少管所待过一阵
He spent some time in juvie.
不过说实话 他不太是我的菜
But, you know, he's not really my type.
就是过渡期的备胎罢了
He's just a rebound.
所以我觉得应该无所谓吧
So I guess it doesn't really matter.
我为什么要告诉你们这些
Why am I even talking to you guys?
快走[树叶]
Leave!
赶紧走
Get out!
你看到她的眼神了吗
Did you see the look in her eyes?
就好像她真的相信她说的一样
Like she believed everything she was saying.
太恐怖了 就好像我大学认识的一个人
That's terrifying. Like this guy I knew in college.
他老是给我讲这些疯狂派对
He was always telling me about these "crazy parties"
说那里到处都是女的
that were "full of women."
可每次我问他派对在哪里
But when I'd ask him where they were,
他都会给我假地址
he'd give me a fake address.
这让我疑惑究竟还有什么是她编出来的
Makes me wonder what else she's making up.
我从来没见过她辅导数学的那个女生
I have never met that girl she turtors in math.
埃丝特·蔡吗 我也没见过
Esther Choi? Me neither.
因为她根本就不存在
Because she doesn't exist!
这世上没有一个叫埃丝特·蔡[华裔]
There is not an Esther Choi on earth
还需要被辅导数学的
who needs math tutoring.
她需要帮助 克莱尔
She needs help, Claire.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
我们该再送她去看那个心理医生吗
I mean, should we send her back to that therapist?
我们从没见过的那个吗
The one we've never met?
不 等等
No! Wait!
别开门 让开
Don't open it! Move away!
是找我的 让开
It's for me! Move!
天啊 你好漂亮
Damn. You look hot.
玫瑰是你送的吗 泰迪
The roses are from you, Teddy?
是啊 我在少管所认识个人在墓地工作
Yeah, I met a guy in juvie who works at the cemetery.
他们那儿到处都是花
They got flowers all over the place.
我还给你带了这个
Oh, I also got you this.
太棒了 走吧
Sweet. Let's go.
另外一个头盔裂了
My other one of these cracked,
你用这个吧
so you can use this one.
好的
Okay.
太好了 我们的乖女儿没疯
Yes! Our little girl isn't crazy!
泰迪是真实存在的
Teddy's real!
-是真的不像好人 -我去追
- Real freaky! - I'm going!
小卡 你在打鼾
Cam, you're snoring.
什么 不好意思
What? Sorry.
是我打鼾吗
Was that me?
天啊 天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
她在这里干什么
What is she doing out here?
-她的腿有睡眠不宁症 -两条都有吗
- Well, she has that restless leg. - Both of them?
天啊 把冰淇淋拿开
Oh, my gosh, get the ice cream!
我们要怎么办 该把她叫起来吗
What do we do? Should we wake her up?
然后说什么
And say what?
能烦请你从沙发上下来吗
"Would you mind terribly getting off our couch?
你貌似在给它涂油
You seem to be glazing it."
你还有更好的主意吗
Do you have a better idea?
好吧 到后面去
Okay, okay, go around the back.
我要怎么做 我要怎么做
What am I doing? What am I doing?
把这个垫到她下面
We'll get this underneath her.
有一次我帮一头母猪在我们家客厅地板上
Once, I helped a sow give birth to nine baby piglets
给八只猪仔接生
on our living room floor.
什么都没沾到油毯上
Didn't get a drop of nothin' on the linoleum.
等下再问你为什么客厅会有只母猪
We're gonna get back to why the sow was in the living room.
我们一起看戴安娜王妃的婚礼直播 太美了
Lady Di's wedding. It was beautiful.
小卡 我们会弄醒她的
Cam, she's gonna wake up.
怎么可能 她吃了那么多安眠药
Oh, please, she's got enough pills in her,
多到可以像响葫芦一样摇响了
she's gonna rattle like a maraca.
把她翻过来
Roll!
道格 不 我不想要
Doug, no, I don't wanna.
好吧 我该怎么办 我该怎么办
Okay, okay, what do I do? What do I do?
你从这边过来
You come back around this way.
不 道格
No, Doug.
现在这么办 我把她往这边推
Now, what we're gonna do is I'll push her this way
然后拉动毯子
and pull the blanket.
好 我得拉她是吗 好
Okay, I got to pull her? Okay.
要掉了 要掉了
I'm losing her. I'm losing her.
这样倒是也行 没问题的
This could work, too. It's fine.
怎 怎么了
What -- what happened?
你刚做恶梦了
You were having a really bad dream,
然后沙发睡着也不太舒服
and then you rolled right off
你就滚下来了
of our uncomfortable sofa.
真抱歉 我太孤独了
I'm sorry. I-I was lonely.
我跑出来
I came out here,
结果把你全家都吵醒了
and then I wound up waking up the whole house.
我简直是世界上最讨人厌的客人
I'm the worst houseguest in the world!
-别别别 -别别别
- Don't. - Don't.
道格说得对 我会孤独终老的
Doug was right. I'm gonna die alone.
-别别别 -别别别
- Don't. - Don't.
过来
Okay, come on.
你能不能安静点儿啊
Can you please be quiet?
真是太抱歉了 莉莉 都是我的错
I'm so sorry, Lily. It's all my fault.
我头疼
My head hurts.
-我去给你拿点止疼药 -好
- I'm gonna get you some aspirin. - Okay.
小卡 我们是不是太坏了
Cam, are we terrible people?
还不是为了保护范德考夫的沙发
For protecting a Vanderkoff?
他去年可是上吊自杀了
He hanged himself last year.
这玩意可是绝版 以后再也不会有了
It's not like they're making more of those.
我们刚刚把一个双相情感障碍的离婚妇女
We just rolled a bipolar divorcee
给滚到硬木地板上去了 还是脸先落地
face-first onto a hardwood floor.
就为了保护个沙发
All to protect a couch.
不只是个沙发 那是我们唯一的好东西
It's not just a couch. Our one nice thing.
我们过去七年一直用着这种油腻腻的台面
The last seven years have been about sticky countertops
丑不拉几的浴帘 还有儿童安全锁
and horsy shower curtains and childproof locks.
你知道这抽屉里是什么东西吗
Do you know what's in this drawer?
我都不知道抽屉里是啥
I don't know what's in this drawer.
完全不知道
I have no idea.
我知道这让人挺不爽的 好吧
Look, I know it's frustrating, all right?
但这不是我们爱惜东西而不爱惜人的理由
But is that really a reason to choose a thing over a person?
拜托 我们简直跟道格是一个档次的
I mean, come on. We're no better than Doug.
我觉得这对莉莉来说的确不是一个好榜样
I guess it's not a great example to set for Lily.
也许我们并不值得拥有这么一件好东西
Maybe we don't deserve one nice thing.
然后太阳升起了 所有的乌龟
"And when the sun came out, all the turtles,
从小A到小Z 都在野餐时愉快地玩耍
from Abner to Zeke, had fun at the picnic."
《乌龟们的下雨天》
"A rainy day for turtles."
这本书总能让莉莉高兴起来
It always makes Lily feel better.
我想她是觉得...
I guess she just thought that...
我们确实拥有一样好东西
We do have one nice thing.
然后一场美丽的雨
"And a beautiful rain--"
我们用不着非得看着它死去 走吧
Well, we don't have to watch it die. Come on.
走吧 杰
Let's go, Jay!
我们二十分钟后就该到野餐地点了
We're supposed to be at the picnic in 20 minutes!
他们在货车里都住了六年
They've been living in a van for six years.
多等一小会儿也不会怎么样
They can wait a little longer.
所以今天我是看不成球赛了
So, today, instead of watching the game,
我得去跟哥伦比亚人在草地上玩飞镖
I'll be playing lawn darts with Colombians,
谢谢你不长脑子
thanks to you not using your brain.
我要看这个 《骗中骗》
Here we go -- "The Sting."
倒是有人是得偿所愿了
Well, someone's getting what they want today.
你终于可以看你的宝贝电影了
You finally get to watch your precious movie, huh?
关于一场漫长骗局的传说
"A classic tale about a long con."
我今天就让给你了
Well, you're welcome.
等一下
Wait a minute.
流氓和出卖朋友的人遍地都是
"Rogues and double-crossers abound.
谁能胜过谁
Who will outsmart whom?"
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你知道我利用狗狗成人礼派对
You knew I was using the bark mitzvah
当做讨价还价的筹码
as a bargaining chip.
所以你才说服歌洛丽亚回去
That's why you talked Gloria into coming back --
所以我就逃不掉这个野餐
So I couldn't weasel my way out of this stupid picnic
然后你就能独占大电视
and you'd get the big TV.
我现在盯上你了
Well, I'm onto you now.
我只不过是在读DVD封面
I was just reading off the DVD box.
你能相信吗
I mean, can you believe
布伦达过来住一晚上就带这么多东西
all the stuff Brenda brought for one night?
是啊 看那一堆东西
I know. Look at all this stuff over here.
超补水唇膏
Super replenishing balm?
毛孔收缩精华液
Uh, pore-reducing booster serum?
抗老化提亮珠珠
Anti-aging buffing beads?
当女人也太累了
It must be so hard to be a girl.
可不是嘛
I know. I know.
真让人担心以后莉莉要怎样
It really makes you worry about the world
应付这个不友好的世界
we're sending Lily out into.
女孩必须要完美无缺 这压力太大了
Well, there's so much pressure on girls to be perfect.
-你好了吗 -好了
- You ready? - Yep.
问题是 小卡
The thing is, Cam,
我们能做的就是把我们的价值观教给她
all we can do is instill our beliefs in her
期望她能做出明智的选择
and hope that she makes good choices.
镇静喷雾要么[冷静点了吗]
Calming mister?
这么谈一谈确实好多了
It does feel nice to talk about it.
不是 这是个镇静喷雾
No, this is a calming mister.
我刚买的
I just bought this.
哦是吗 要的
Oh, god, yes.
试试
Wanna try it?